<questions>
	<question>
		<text>
		You have a webjob named WebJob1 that is deployed in an Azure web app named WebApp1.{##}You plan to schedule the webjob as a continuous webjob.{##}
		You need to design a solution that always allow the webjob to execute successfully.{##}Which action should you perform on WebApp1?
		</text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
		  Enable Always On
		  </answer>
      <answer>
		  Enable Web Sockets
		  </answer>
      <answer>
		  Create a new deployment slot
		  </answer>
      <answer>
		  Create a new Cross Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) allowed origin
		  </answer>      
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are planning and designing a new Microsoft Azure web app.{##}You need to ensure that the developers can quickly make a staging version of the web app live. In the event of an unforseen 
		problem, they need to be able to quickly revert the web app back to the previous version with minimal downtime.{##}What should you include in the planning phase?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Deployment from source control
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Deployment slots
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Publishing profiles
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Linked resources
		  </answer>
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You have an Azure web app.{##}The web app is built by using ASP.Net MVC and contains a Web API controller.{##}You need to design a solution that will allow other web apps to access the Web API 
		controller by using access keys.{##}The solution must minimize the amount of implementation time required.{##}Which technology should be use?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Active Directory Premium
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Role-based Access Control (RBAC) custom roles
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  API Management
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Active Directory Standard
		  </answer>
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are designing the architecture of an Azure web app. You plan to use a blob storage container to store files collected by the web app.{##}You need to ensure that the files are available in the event of an outage 
		of the datacenter in which the container is located. The solution must minimize cost.{##}Which storage type should you use?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Zone-redundant storage (ZRS)
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  read-access geo-redundant storage (RA-GRS)
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Geo-redundant storage (GRS)
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Locally redundant storage (LRS)
		  </answer>
    </answers>
    
	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are migrating a proprietary database to Azure. The proprietary databse is an indexed binary file.{##}Which resource should you use to store the databse?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Queue
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Table
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  SQL Database
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Blob
		  </answer>
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are designing an application to carry out facial recognition on photographs uploaded by users. The photographs are placced in a queue and picked up for processing by a custom service. The application 
		may take several hours to complete its processing. The application then notifies users by email that the job is complete.{##}Which Azure Service or feature should you use for processing of the photographs.
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Azure web role
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Service Bus queue
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure queue
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Azure worker role
		  </answer>
    </answers>
    
	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are the security administrator for a bank. You have a website named WebApp1 that customers use for banking-related activities. The website and its associated resources are hosted in Azure.{##}WebApp1 runs 
		on Internet Information Services (IIS) but is NOT published through an Azure Active Directory App Proxy.{##}You need to implement a password reset solution. The solution must verify a user's identity either by 
		sending a text message to the user's mobile device or by using a phone call with a custom greeting.{##}What should you implement?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Mult-factor authentication in the cloud
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Deep Security SaaS
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  A multi-factor authentication server
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure AD Identity Protection
		  </answer>      
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		Provides simple, powerful SQL like language for querying telemetry data collected from server-side and client-side information.
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Application Insights
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  System Center Operations Manager
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Log Analytics
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Swagger API
		  </answer>      
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
    These sections are designed in such a way that a failure of one is extremely unlikely to affect any other(s). 
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Update Domains
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Fault Domains
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Domain Controllers
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Datacenter
		  </answer>      
    </answers>

	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
    An open-source framework for describing, consuming and visualizing API services
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Swashbuckle
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Swagger UI
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Swagger
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure API Apps
		  </answer>      
    </answers>

	</question>
</questions>