<questions>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are planning and designing a new Microsoft Azure web app.{##}You need to ensure that the developers can quickly make a staging version of the web app live. In the event of an unforseen 
		problem, they need to be able to quickly{##}revert the web app back to the previous version with minimal downtime.{##}What should you include in the planning phase?
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Deplpoyment from source control
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Deployment slots
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Publishing profiles
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Linked resources
		  </answer>
    </answers>
	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		You are designing an application to carry out facial recognition on photographs uploaded by users. The photographs are placed in a queue and picked up for processing by a custom service.{##}The application 
		may take several hours to complete its processing. The application then notifies users by email that the job is complete.{##}Which Azure Service or feature should you use for processing of the photographs.
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer>
		  Azure web role
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Service Bus queue
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure queue
		  </answer>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Azure worker role
		  </answer>
    </answers>
	</question>
	<question>
		<text>
		Provides simple, powerful SQL like language for querying telemetry data collected from server-side and client-side information.
		</text>
    <answers>
		  <answer correct="1">
		  Application Insights
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  System Center Operations Manager
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Azure Log Analytics
		  </answer>
		  <answer>
		  Swagger API
		  </answer>      
    </answers>
	</question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Which of the following is a principle within the Agile Manifesto?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Our highest priority is to satisfy the customer through early and continuous delivery of valuable software.
      </answer>
      <answer>
        DevOps not only requires collaboration between teams, but it will organically foster further collaboration between them.
      </answer>
      <answer>
        The union of people, process, and products to enable continuous delivery of value to our end users.
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Software development is business critical – delays have a ‘real’ cost to the business.   Arriving too late means you miss the opportunities.
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Deploy, manage, and monitor all the resources as a group is possible using:
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Azure Resource Manager
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Visual Studio Team Services combined with DevOps
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Platform as a Service
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Azure Portal
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Which file will you use to deploy a database schema from an local, existing SQL Server Database to an Azure SQL Database?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        .dacpac
      </answer>
      <answer>
        .bakpak
      </answer>
      <answer>
        .tupac
      </answer>
      <answer>
        .azbak
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Which Azure SQL Database feature asynchronously replicates committed transactions from a database to another database.
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Active Geo-Replication
      </answer>
      <answer>
        PowerShell
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Geo-Restore
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Elastic Pool
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Which is a factor that may prevent you from adopting a PaaS model and choosing IaaS?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Need to install third-party software
      </answer>
      <answer>
        PowerShell
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Geo-Restore
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Elastic Pool
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      This feature display work items as cards, rather than a list.
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Kanban Board
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Epic
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Stories
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Swimlanes
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>
      Why should you estimate velocity and perform forecasting for work?
    </text> 
    <answers>
      <answer correct="1">
        Determines how much work to perform sprint-over-sprint
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Track and organize data by using queries 
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Set WIP limits to monitor flow
      </answer>
      <answer>
        Effective means of communication between product managers and developers
      </answer>
    </answers>
  </question>

</questions>